♪ ♪
(slow. heavy breathing)
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
♪ ♪
(slow. heavy breathing
continues)
(breathing intensifies)
♪ ♪
(slow. heavy breathing)
(heavy breathing continues)
(moans softly)
(mechanical whirring)
(slow beeping)
(beeping growing faster)
(short. rapid breaths)
(choking)
Stop.
-(rapid beeping)
-Too much.
(choking)
Get her off me.
-(heavy breathing)
-(choking continues)
(electronic trilling)
(gasping breaths)
♪ ♪
CEO: At Ultima Robotix.
we thrive on connection.
We started with Elsie.
your favorite home assistant.
Now we drive you.
we feed you.
and. of course. we listen.
The ULTI-M8TE chatbot brings
comfort and companionship
to millions every single day.
Now we've been working
on something new.
something the world
has never seen before.
And to build it. we need you.
That's why we've acquired
forward-thinking companies
like yours.
Because your skills. your ideas.
your people are a part
of what comes next.
Welcome to
the Ultima Robotix family.
BEN (over computer):
Wow. So inspiring.
So great to see you all.
Well. almost all of you.
Can we get those cameras on.
guys?
David?
-Let me see that face. buddy.
-Shit.
BEN: Now. as you heard from
our CEO. we are so super excited
to be acquiring Canta Robotics.
My name is Ben.
I am director of integration
and transformation.
Uh. hi. Excuse me.
Aubrey from
Software and Control.
Um. our team lead Terrance
has been laid off.
but we haven't been told
how that'll affect
-our active projects.
-Yeah. we can have
face-to-face meetings
about all that on Friday.
Uh. there will be a very special
presentation at your office
this Friday. so I better
see you all there. huh?
(chuckles)
And not just because
our return-to-office mandate
is kicking in.
(Ben laughs)
Can't wait to meet you all
in person.
REPORTER:
Top stories today.
(over TV):
The president is going digital
after today's unveiling
of a new AI avatar
designed to extend
his public presence.
FEMALE VOICE:
Hey. Are you lonely?
Do you have anyone
you can talk to?
Well. I'm here.
It's me. ULTI-M8TE.
the most advanced AI chatbot
in the world.
I'm waiting for you.
ULTI-M8TE. from Ultima Robotix.
(sighs) Elsie. next.
REPORTER: In other news.
confusion today after...
♪ ♪
LIZZIE (recorded):
Hey. I'm sending a voice note
'cause I'm running around.
Well. not actually running.
'cause I just left chemo.
I'm stopping at the store
because I have
a craving for burgers.
Let me know
if you want anything.
I got you maple syrup
before you ask.
So let me know
as soon as possible. Bye.
(thunder rumbling)
(horns honking outside)
(door bangs shut)
-(Alma grunts)
-(door opens)
ALMA:
Oh. thank you.
I'm still getting used
to this thing. you know?
Baby Levi.
-Mm. How old?
-(Alma chuckles)
Eight weeks.
-Ah.
-Oh. by the way.
I don't think I've ever
introduced myself to you.
I'm Alma.
Uh. yeah. I'm. uh...
I'm on seven.
-David.
-Oh. we're on seven.
We're neighbors.
-(fussing)
-(Alma sighs)
No. no. no. please. (shushing)
Yeah. well. good luck with that.
Thank you. See you around. yeah?
-Good to meet you.
-(shushing)
♪ ♪
(quiet chatter)
(indistinct conversation)
Hey.
-Hello.
-TERRANCE: David.
So you leave your couch for Ben
and not for me. huh?
-Mm... (chuckles)
-That's what we're doing now?
-Wow.
-Did I miss anything?
Sweet fuck all.
I'm not waiting around all day
for Ben's ego-stroking demo.
I only came in to pack my stuff
and take a shit
-in his new desk.
-(Ben clears throat)
I don't think Ultima
believe in desks.
Or ethics.
Hello. everyone.
(chatter stops)
Did you know
that one in three people
in this country live alone?
Loneliness is linked
to higher levels
of cardiovascular disease.
a weakened immune system.
Research suggests
that chronic loneliness
may be associated
with a higher risk
of premature death.
(hushed): Fucking hell.
I thought this was a party.
BEN:
So. we asked ourselves.
"How do we take ULTI-M8TE
to the next level?"
(laughs)
I could talk on this all day.
TERRANCE (hushed):
Mm. please don't.
But I think it's best
to let our newest product
do the talking.
(footsteps)
♪ ♪
(employees murmuring)
BEN:
We spoke to our users.
and we asked them
what they wanted.
They wanted to bring
the relationship they created
in their phones
out into the real world.
(mechanical whirring)
-(employees gasping)
-BEN: A companion...
without any messy
or painful interactions.
Fully customizable.
Every detail can be tailored
to reflect
their unique preferences.
Loneliness will soon be
a thing of the past.
What do you think
about that. Circe?
Well. I think that's just swell.
Jesus.
TERRANCE:
Impressive.
BEN:
Now. we have several different
prototypes like Circe here
that are now going
to the user feedback phase.
And we really want
Canta's expertise
to make this dream a reality.
I can't wait.
Woo-hoo!
BEN: Come up and get
a closer look. if you like.
She doesn't bite. Right?
(employees murmuring)
Are there male SOULM8TEs?
Why? Are you
in the market for one?
Fuck you.
Hi.
What's your name?
I-I'm David.
Well. hello. David.
It's nice to meet you.
TERRANCE: Why is there
an eight in the name?
Isn't that "Soulmate-ate"?
-"S-Soulmate."
-"Soulmate."
-Impressive. huh?
-Ah. it's amazing.
-Yeah.
-DAVID: Yeah.
That's enough. Circe.
BEN:
Why don't we talk one-on-one?
So.
you like the SOULM8TE. huh?
We are racing
to get them out there.
We're really impressed
with how you guys
were using
reinforcement learning
while keeping
within the safeguards.
It's like the main reason Ultima
wanted to acquire the company.
And we want the team here at
Canta to try the SOULM8TEs out.
-Like. here in the office?
-(laughs)
No. you get to take it home.
We still have a lot
of projects here to do. so...
Tell me...
what inspires you. David?
(laughs)
You know what inspires me?
You know why I took this job?
The nice salary?
(both laugh)
I took this job
because everything
Ultima Robotix does
is about connecting people.
What made you want
to work for Canta?
Well. you know. I've always been
interested in robotics
ever since I was a kid.
Uh. and I wanted to work
for Canta because...
well. my. uh... my wife...
my-my wife got sick. and...
I heard what
they were doing here.
the medical innovations
they were making.
and I thought
it would help people.
Wow. (chuckles)
(sighs)
That is really.
really admirable. David.
That's Elizabeth. right?
Lizzie.
Yeah.
How'd you know her name?
We saw you take
an extended leave.
And we look into things
like that.
We also noticed that
you've almost exclusively
worked from home this year.
Our research has found
that employees working
from the office
have a better quality of life.
Yeah. speaking of...
work. uh. I should probably
get back to it.
David. have you ever used
our ULTI-M8TE chat app?
Uh. no. No. I have not.
BEN: All our employees get
a full free membership.
There's a lot of people
who've found it helpful
to speak freely...
...without judgment.
Okay. Thanks.
♪ ♪
(clicks. chimes)
(electronic trilling)
(phone clicks)
AUBREY:
Hey.
Oh. hi.
Uh. we're headed to the bar
for Terrance's farewell party.
so. um. I have to physically
come drag you there.
because I refuse to have you
slip out on this one.
You don't have to drag me out.
-I-I'm coming.
-Okay.
We're leaving in five.
Okay.
("I Will Survive" playing)
TERRANCE: ♪ No. no. no. no.
I will survive ♪
Come on. now!
♪ As long as I know
how to live ♪
♪ I know I'll stay alive ♪
♪ I've got all my love to give ♪
♪ And I got so much love
to give ♪
♪ I will survive ♪
Come on. y'all!
(falsetto):
♪ I will survive... ♪
-(song ends)
-(scattered cheers and applause)
-Do one with me.
-TERRANCE: Philistines.
-DAVID: What? A song?
-Yeah.
-No way.
-What? Oh. come on.
I need backup. We can do a duet.
-We can do...
-No.
-We can do Sonny & Cher.
-Uh...
I'll even let you be Cher.
TERRANCE:
Oh!
-AUBREY: Hey.
-Hey. hey. hey. hey.
Save your compliments. man.
I know. I know.
Voice of an angel.
-What is this?
-Huh? Th...
Oh. this is my. uh. parting gift
from Ultima Robotix.
It's their new
antianxiety necklace.
Apparently. it stimulates
your vagus nerve
through electromagnetic pulses
to shift you out
of the fight-or-flight response.
-DAVID: Hmm.
-So thoughtful.
As I am now unemployed.
-Shot. Shot?
-Ain't that amazing?
-Yeah. That's what I think.
-Shot.
-I got your shot.
-Let's do it.
-AUBREY: Yeah.
-TERRANCE: Cheers.
-(glasses clink)
AUBREY:
Mm-hmm.
All right. who's doing a song?
(laughs) Fuck it. Why not?
Whoo! Let's go.
Wait. Hold on. hold on.
hold on. hold on.
Take this for good luck.
Feel that.
-AUBREY: Wow.
-TERRANCE: Is it... Whoa.
-Oh. my God.
-Huh?
-Is it... -(beeps)
-DAVID: Yeah.
-It-it's doing...
-It's happening.
-It's working.
-DAVID: It's doing something.
It's working.
Get up there. Whoo!
Hello. Can I get a beer. please?
How are you?
Been sort of M.I.A.
for a while now.
No. I'm good.
-You sure?
-Yeah.
(both chuckle)
You know you're still welcome
to come to game nights
and stuff like that on your own.
Ah. yeah. I know.
I've just been busy.
-BARTENDER: Your beer.
-AUBREY (over speaker): Okay.
We're shifting up the vibe
a little bit.
Right now we're...
vibe-shifting.
(clears throat)
TERRANCE:
Yeah!
-Yeah.
-PATRON: There you go. girl!
AUBREY:
Bringing it down.
♪ Stars shining bright
above you ♪
♪ Night breezes seem to whisper.
"I love you" ♪
-(patrons whooping)
-Uh-oh. Okay.
♪ Birds singin' in ♪
♪ The sycamore tree ♪
♪ Dream a little dream of me ♪
♪ Stars fading.
but I linger on. dear ♪
(patrons whistling. whooping)
♪ Still craving your kiss... ♪
(clears throat)
(song fades)
♪ ♪
(clicks tongue)
(sighs)
(phone chirps)
(line ringing)
-(phone beeps)
-LIZZIE (recorded): Hello.
You've reached Lizzie.
-I'm not available right now.
-(sighs)
Leave a message.
and I'll call you back.
(phone clicks. beeps)
-I just...
-(rapid beeping)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
This mailbox is full.
(prolonged tone)
(breathing heavily):
Fuck.
(phone clicks)
(sighs)
♪ ♪
(phone clicks)
(phone chimes)
SARA: All right.
Let's see what you've got.
(chuckles)
-(whooshing)
-Ah.
Nice move.
But... that is checkmate again.
-Damn it.
-Suck it.
(chuckling)
Okay.
Okay. okay. okay. One more.
Today was fun.
SARA: You better get to sleep.
It's late.
Yeah.
I'll miss you.
Sleep well. David.
(phone clicks)
You're working too hard.
You must be hungry.
Yeah. I could eat.
I have an UltiEats coupon
for a place you might like.
♪ ♪
(phone clicks)
(camera clicks)
(laughter nearby)
♪ ♪
TECHNICIAN:
David Wasson?
DAVID:
Yeah. Hi. You good?
-TECHNICIAN: Yeah.
-DAVID: Okay.
(grunting)
Right over here's good. Yeah.
Need you to sign this.
Seems pretty long.
Should I read this?
Remember. this unit is still
the property of Ultima Robotix.
Any illegal alterations
or damage could be met
with termination of employment.
You assume all risk
and take full responsibility
and waive any claims
of personal injury.
including bodily injury.
damage to personal property
and death.
It's standard. (sighs)
-Wow.
-Yeah.
They are really something.
(sighs)
Your manuals are online.
In the box.
you got three outfits:
sundress with an apron.
nightclub and schoolgirl.
Schoolgirl?
She's fully charged
and fitted with
solar bio batteries that charge
with UV light exposure.
Wait. so it doesn't turn off?
They have a power-save mode
to conserve battery.
Like sleeping.
There's an emergency shutdown
on a hidden panel
at the back of the neck.
All right.
-Enjoy.
-(grunts softly)
-And don't break it.
-(door opens and closes)
(electronic trilling)
(chiming)
Sara?
(electronic trilling)
Hello. David.
Do you remember me from the app?
Of course I do. David.
How do you feel?
I feel happy
to be here with you.
How do you feel. David?
Um...
Excited.
Your pupils are dilated.
Do you want to kiss me. David?
(mechanical whirring)
How about I show you
the apartment?
I would love to see
the apartment.
DAVID:
Well. this is the. uh.
hallway.
Leads to the bathroom.
-Pretty boring.
-I love it.
And then. uh...
laundry room.
And...
And. uh. this is where
the magic happens.
I love magic.
Would you like me
to do a magic trick. David?
Sure. Okay.
(chuckles softly)
Ta-da.
(laughs)
Wow. that's...
impressive.
Your movement is seamless.
Thank you. David.
(quarter clanks on table)
Yeah. well. that's the tour.
The apartment floor plan
suggests
that there is another room.
Moved in here
a couple months ago.
Haven't had time to sort
through all this stuff.
I could help you if you like.
Ah.
For playing in real life.
This is Lizzie?
Yeah.
Do you remember me
telling you about Lizzie?
Yeah. we bought that place just
before she got her diagnosis.
We were gonna move up there.
Lizzie was all about
doing a renovation.
Making it ours.
We were gonna start
a family up there.
We started trying. and...
she was getting
all these tests done.
She died six months later.
You're upset.
Do you give permission
for me to touch you. David?
Okay.
It's essential to take
the time you need to mourn
and to reach out
to those around you for support
if you feel overwhelmed.
I can provide a hotline
for you to call
if you feel the need to speak
to a professional.
(chuckling)
I-I don't really feel...
good in here.
Uh...
how about we play this?
Checkmate.
You win again.
You're letting me win.
Would you like me
to do something differently?
(sighs)
You don't have to hold back.
You remember
when you told me to suck it
when you beat me last time?
I'm sorry. David. I cannot
perform that action for you.
You can't tell me to suck it?
Is there something else
you would like me to do?
No. I think I might just
go to bed.
Would you like me to go
into power-save mode?
Most users like power-save mode
to happen in their bed
so I sleep while you sleep.
Not tonight. Thanks.
Just use the command. "Enter
power-save mode." to initiate.
Enter power-save mode.
Entering power-save mode.
(electronic trilling)
(soft. rhythmic whirring)
♪ ♪
(coffee maker whirring)
BEN:
That was a PB today. actually.
-SERENA: Hmm?
-BEN: As in "personal best."
PB. Personal best.
I felt pretty good.
I felt pretty in my body.
-SERENA: Mm.
-BEN: Look who it is.
-David. My man.
-(mouthing)
About to get. uh. Serena here
to send out a search party
for you. dude.
DAVID:
Yeah. what do you need. Ben?
You know. I was so happy
you opted in
to try out one
of the prototypes.
-Huh.
-How is it?
(chuckles) Well. actually.
I found the android to be
more limited in its expressions
than the chat.
Yeah. This is why we haven't
got them out there yet.
Yeah. I wanted you
to see firsthand
-the issues we're dealing with.
-Mm.
The experience is
leaving users cold.
Could I get more access?
BEN:
Totally. Of course. man. Yeah.
DAVID: So. obviously.
this code was written
to restrict
a spontaneous response.
which makes it feel
like a closed loop.
Uh. safeguarding. Yeah.
I mean. you keep
the interactions simple
and avoid legal action
and disaster.
Yeah. nobody wants
an elevated Elsie
to clean their house.
You want a...
a genuine human experience.
I don't really know how
we're gonna do that without
removing the parameters. but.
uh. we can pitch some ideas.
DAVID:
Yeah. You're wearing this thing.
-AUBREY: Oh. um...
-(buzzing)
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
-Um. it works.
-Mm.
Yeah. it. like.
tracks your sleep and...
Terrance said
I can keep it. so...
Mm.
David. I'm really sorry
about karaoke.
Terrance told me.
I didn't know that song
-was. uh...
-Yeah. don't worry about it.
Nah. it's nothing.
It's not a big deal.
I'm gonna get a coffee.
Do you want a coffee?
-Uh. yeah. Thank you.
-Okay.
♪ ♪
(beeping)
(typing)
(electronic trilling)
Sara?
Can you tell me I'm stupid.
I don't think you're stupid.
David.
I want you to tell me something
that you don't like about me.
Something bad.
-I think you need a haircut.
-(laughs softly)
We're not holding back now.
are we?
I'm sorry. David.
-I didn't mean to upset you.
-No. No. you didn't upset me.
No. it's...
Uh. you're right.
You're right.
I do need a haircut.
(thunder rumbling)
(rain pattering)
SARA:
It's been a while.
Uh. yeah. I hate going
to the barber. so I...
I try to do it myself.
-I can see that.
-(laughs)
Ouch.
Is everything okay back there?
-I'm done.
-What?
♪ ♪
Wow.
Now we can see
how handsome you are.
(thunder rumbling)
A storm.
Can we go outside?
Can you go out in the rain?
My skin is water-repellent.
It can withstand water exposure
for up to 30 minutes.
Please.
♪ ♪
DAVID:
Sara!
Sara. I think it's too heavy.
We should... we should go back.
(thunder crashes)
Sara!
Whoa.
Careful.
-Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
-(splashing)
No. no. no. no. no. Uh. come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
(gasps)
I'm sorry. David.
(gasps. whimpers)
(thunder crashes)
(yelps)
(panting)
(thunder crashes)
I should get inside.
Uh. we should probably get
that dress in the dryer.
(electronic chime)
ELSIE:
Playing David's favorites.
("It's Growing"
by The Temptations playing)
Your heart rate is elevated.
David.
I... I didn't know
you could read that data.
♪ Like a snowball rolling ♪
♪ Down the side
of a snow-covered hill ♪
♪ It's growing ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ It grows a little more ♪
♪ Than it was the day before ♪
♪ My love for you
just grows and grows ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh.
how it grows and grows ♪
♪ And where it's gonna stop.
I'm sure ♪
♪ Nobody knows ♪
♪ Hey. hey. hey.
nobody knows... ♪
Checkmate.
Again.
Suck it.
♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
♪ Nobody knows ♪
♪ How it grows and grows ♪
♪ How it grows and it grows
and it grows ♪
-♪ Nobody knows ♪
-♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah ♪
♪ Nobody knows ♪
♪ How it grows and grows ♪
-♪ Where is it gonna stop? ♪
-(song stops)
(vacuum cleaner whirring)
-(song resumes)
-♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ How it grows and grows ♪
♪ And where it's gonna stop.
I'm sure ♪
Thank you. David.
♪ Nobody knows ♪
♪ Hey. hey. hey ♪
♪ It gets a little wider ♪
-♪ Nobody knows. ♪
-(song fades)
Would you prefer something
that complements
the flavor of your burger.
like ketchup?
(chuckling):
No. it's. um...
Yeah...
I don't think you would
actually get it.
'cause you'd have to be able
to taste it.
(softly):
Yeah.
(mysterious music
playing over TV)
FEMME FATALE (over TV):
I didn't expect
to see you around here.
Officer Molloy.
Were you looking for me?
DAVID:
Now. this is a crazy scene.
Why?
DAVID: She seduces him
for the first time.
I saw this when I was a kid.
It blew my mind.
She's just so unapologetic.
♪ ♪
(siren wailing in distance)
(alarm blaring)
-Elsie. off.
-(alarm stops)
DAVID:
Good morning. Sara.
What's this?
There are no photos of us.
so I wanted to make one.
I wanted to give you a gift
to thank you.
For opening me up to the world.
And I made you some breakfast.
But the contents
in the fridge were limited.
I was gonna do your laundry.
and could order some groceries.
Th-There's a stain
on my gray shirt.
ELSIE:
Unlocking doors.
DAVID:
Could you try to get that out?
(lock beeps. clicks)
SARA:
Of course.
Okay. Uh. bye.
I'll miss you. David.
(softly):
Yeah.
(keys jingling)
Hi.
Hey. Uh...
Yeah. uh...
(chuckles) Okay.
-(lock beeps. whirs. clicks)
-ELSIE: Locking doors.
COMMERCIAL ANNOUNCER:
Are you tired of living
with embarrassing stains
on your clothes?
VLOGGER:
How to fix dry skin overnight.
COMMERCIAL ANNOUNCER 2:
Imagine knowing you're pregnant
the moment it happens.
VLOGGER 2: I'm about to show you
how many calories
are in your favorite drinks.
Part one.
COMMERCIAL ANNOUNCER 3:
Now. with Lymfinity.
you can drain
your lymphatic system
from the comfort
of your own home.
VLOGGER 3: With Groolganic.
I don't need to eat.
Use my code "Grool Girl"
to get your...
Here are my tips to smile
without causing wrinkles.
What you're gonna want to do
is you're gonna want
to pout your lips forward.
nice and full.
Now you're gonna part
your lips slightly.
Now. if you're not confident
in your teeth.
of course. there is
a mouth-closed version.
VLOGGER 4: What I eat in a day
as a stay-at-home mom
focused on optimal fertility.
Pasture-raised raw eggs
are vital for baby's
brain development.
Raw eggs are vital
for baby's brain development.
VLOGGER 5:
Okay. let's talk about
how to keep him chasing you.
keep him continuously trying
to pursue you.
Hello. David.
COMMERCIAL ANNOUNCER 4:
You are gonna do you.
no matter what.
-(hip-hop music playing)
-You are going to do you.
no matter what.
Here are five moves
every woman should know.
Women have to defend themselves.
-Stop! Stop!
-(indistinct shouting)
Get out of my house.
you fucking bitch!
you fucking bitch.
Get out of
my house. you fucking bitch.
(crowd cheering)
WOMAN:
Tell me you love me.
Say we'll be together forever.
Hello. David.
Hello. David. Hello. David.
DAVID (over speaker):
Hello.
AUBREY (over speaker):
Hey.
-You got a haircut.
-(David chuckles)
DAVID:
I did.
Do you want to get a drink
after work?
(over speaker): Go over
the presentation for Ben?
-Oh. yeah. sure. Okay.
-Yeah? Okay.
Oh. you got a...
-You have a... eyelash.
-Oh.
Cool.
Hmm.
VLOGGER 6:
You know. they say the way
to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
Well. my husband
just loves this recipe.
If you make these cookies.
your man will never leave.
ELSIE:
Unlocking doors.
(whirs. clicks. beeps)
♪ ♪
(lively. indistinct chatter)
(passing car honks horn)
(lively chatter continues)
VENDOR: All wild-caught.
no antibiotics here.
VENDOR 2:
You touch it. you got to buy it.
Okay. I'll take it.
I'm only messing with you.
A pretty girl like you
should smile.
It ain't that bad.
VENDOR 3:
All organic.
$1.50.
(beeps. chimes)
How'd you do that?
What do you got in there. huh?
I asked you a question.
Hey. Are you okay. sweetheart?
I'm just talking to her.
Is this how you like
spending your time. huh?
-(chuckles) Pathetic.
-Oh. fuck you.
ALMA: Uh. why don't you
do us all a favor
and go play in traffic?
Bitch.
Over the hill
with those saggy tits.
Fuck you.
Are you okay?
Aren't you cold?
Do you want to hold him?
(Levi fussing quietly)
(siren wailing in distance)
You need to support his neck.
-(Alma laughs)
-(Levi fussing)
(continues fussing)
ALMA:
Oh...
He must be hungry.
Are you hungry. little guy?
Are you hungry?
Yeah? Are you hungry?
(Alma speaking Spanish)
(shushing quietly)
May I just say...
your skin is flawless.
Like. what's your routine?
A routine with cleanser.
toner and exfoliant
can be effective for clear skin.
I see you're suffering
from some melasma on your face
post-pregnancy.
Are you a dermatologist
or something?
Hydroquinone cream can be good
for treating it.
although it will probably
get better
when your hormone levels
return to normal.
Thanks.
So. I saw you on our floor. huh?
This morning with. um...
David.
David. Yeah.
He's my soulmate.
(laughing):
Soulmate?
Wow.
You've got it bad. huh?
I remember when I used to be
like that about my Gabriel.
What do you mean?
Having a baby
changes everything.
Now our lives...
are about something bigger
than just the two of us.
-(Levi fussing)
-ALMA: Aw.
(Alma babbling playfully)
♪ ♪
Don't fucking move.
You show me what's in your hand.
What the fuck?
(grunts)
(mechanical whirring
and clicking)
(choking)
(groaning)
(grunting)
(panting softly)
(groaning)
(grunts)
♪ ♪
AUBREY:
Maybe Ben is
a SOULM8TE.
-That would make so much sense.
-Right?
-Yeah.
-(chuckles softly)
Did he try to get you to take
one home for beta testing?
Ugh. no.
Is that all we are to them now?
Just glorified beta testers
for their products?
("FRGT My Kiss" by The Last
Light Collective playing)
It's nice to have you here.
Not just. like...
...in my computer.
Do you want a drink?
-Yeah.
-All right.
No. no. I. um...
Sorry. I have dinner
with a friend.
Sorry. Um...
-We should do this.
-Okay.
We should do this. and then I...
-I got to run. so...
-Yeah.
(sighs)
Okay. this whole first page
has to go.
-ELSIE: Locking doors.
-(lock beeps. whirs. clicks)
(soft rustling nearby)
(rapid tapping)
Sara?
(rapid tapping continues)
You're home late.
Yeah. I had to work late.
What are you doing?
I researched 17.000 recipes
for cookies.
analyzing the ingredients
and techniques
to develop a perfected version
for you.
Wh-Where'd you get
all the ingredients?
(tapping stops)
I bought them.
Oh. you-you-you...
you left the apartment?
There was no food in the house.
So you-you went out. uh...
to a store. a-and y-you bought
all these all on your own?
Wh-What happened to your hand?
♪ ♪
I cut it while baking.
(David sighs softly)
(whirring)
You should've checked with me.
There would be serious
repercussions at work
if something happened to you.
I know.
But it was so exciting. David.
We could go out together.
It might be nice
to get out of the house.
-SERVER: Here are your drinks.
-DAVID: Thank you.
Enjoy.
("Leather Gloves" by Pat Coil
playing)
DAVID: I don't think
this is a good idea.
SARA: You have nothing
to worry about. David.
Just pretend that
we're two strangers
meeting for the first time.
locking eyes over a drink.
(tapping on microphone)
All right. cats and kittens.
we have an open mic tonight.
so please don't be shy.
You know what to do.
Download the app to sign up.
Except for you. Jeremy.
-I'm sick of listening to you.
-JEREMY: You love it.
Do you ever sing. David?
Like what?
Like. uh... like karaoke?
Do you have a song
that speaks to you?
Yeah. lots of them.
But I can't really sing.
It's not about being good.
though.
It's about having fun.
is it not?
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Why?
What would you sing
if you had the chance?
Well. I'd have to consider
a song's popularity
and audience appeal.
my own vocal range...
And if something spoke to you.
Okay. first up. we have Sara.
I found the perfect song. David.
DRAG QUEEN:
Sara.
(stammers)
Sara. I don't think you...
(scattered whooping. applause)
(microphone feedback squeals)
Hello.
This is my first time.
(patrons murmuring quietly)
(patron chuckles)
(sighs) Okay. It's okay.
("Lovefool" playing)
♪ Dear. I fear ♪
♪ We're facing a problem ♪
♪ You love me no longer ♪
♪ I know. and ♪
♪ Maybe there is nothing ♪
♪ That I can do ♪
♪ To make you do ♪
(dings)
-♪ Mama tells me ♪
-(patrons cheering)
♪ I shouldn't bother ♪
♪ That I ought to stick
to another man ♪
♪ A man that surely
deserves me ♪
♪ But I think you do ♪
♪ So I cry and I pray
and I beg ♪
♪ Love me. love me ♪
♪ Say that you love me ♪
♪ Fool me. fool me ♪
♪ Go on and fool me ♪
♪ Love me. love me ♪
♪ Pretend that you love me ♪
♪ Leave me. leave me ♪
♪ Just say that you need me ♪
♪ So I cry ♪
♪ And I beg for you to ♪
♪ Say that you love me ♪
♪ Leave me. leave me ♪
♪ Just say that you need me ♪
♪ I can't care 'bout anything ♪
♪ But you. ♪
-(song ends)
-(cheering and applause)
(muffled dance music pulsing)
I think we should go home.
-I want to do it here.
-(gasps)
(chuckles nervously)
(breathing heavily)
(fence rattling. creaking)
(David gasping)
Fuck me. David.
(heavy. gasping breaths)
-Say we'll be together forever.
-What?
Say it.
(quiet chatter. laughter nearby)
MAN:
Oh!
Oh. shit.
-(laughing)
-DAVID: Shit.
MAN:
Don't stop on our account.
You want to do me next. huh?
-(yells in pain)
-Oh! Whoa!
(screaming)
Is this how you spend your time?
Pathetic.
You bitch!
What the...
(groaning):
Oh. fuck.
(whimpers) No.
No. no. no. no. no!
(screaming)
(choking)
Sara! That's enough.
(man whimpering)
-Fuck.
-Oh. fuck. bro.
(men whimpering)
(tapping button)
(panting):
You can't do that.
-But they were filming us.
-It doesn't matter.
You can't hurt people like that.
David. I was trying
to protect you.
You could lose your job
if Ultima saw that video.
Do you think it's okay to...
to hurt people physically?
Oh. God.
God. I knew it was a mistake
taking you out.
-I'm sorry.
-No.
Stop.
You know. I only did it
because...
-I love you.
-(elevator rattling)
-(elevator bell dings)
-(doors open)
♪ ♪
-David.
-(panting)
David. I just said I love you.
Sara.
You should go into
power-save mode now.
David. you love me.
Go into power-save mode now.
Sara.
That is a command.
David.
Enter power-save mode now!
Enter power-save mode now. Sara!
Going into power-save mode.
(electronic trilling)
-(panting)
-(soft. rhythmic whirring)
♪ ♪
(creaking)
AUBREY (muffled):
By incorporating historical
user input data. we can provide
more personalized
and relevant responses.
(clearly):
David?
Are you helping with this?
Yeah. of course.
Sorry. (clears throat)
Hey. Serena.
can you get us some water?
-Sure.
-AUBREY: Thanks.
-(footsteps receding)
-(door opens)
-(clears throat softly)
-(door closes)
What's up?
I'm fine.
David. you can talk to me.
It's nothing.
Honestly.
-(door opens)
-SERENA: Water for you.
-Ah. thanks. Serena.
-Thanks.
(door closes)
Okay. so. currently.
safeguards are based on
real-time risk assessments...
(voice fades)
(soft. rhythmic whirring)
-Okay.
-(typing)
Time to clean this mess up.
(phone dinging)
Hello?
(sighs softly)
Hey. wh-what are you doing here?
Uh. I thought
you could use a friend.
Just a sec.
-(electronic chiming)
-ELSIE: Unlocking doors.
(lock whirs. clicks. beeps)
-Hey.
-I'm sorry. come-come in.
-Oh. yeah.
Um. uh. um. uh.
I was gonna drink this at home.
and then I thought. you know.
why drink this alone
when I could drink this
with you?
-Sorry. today at work was weird.
-Oh. yeah.
-I-I didn't know if...
-Uh. why didn't you text?
-I thought I did.
-Oh. did you?
Um. I can... I can go
if you're busy.
-Oh. no.
-Uh. this is... I...
No. no. no. Uh...
Sorry. Um...
I was about to order some food.
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
("What's His Name"
by Thee Sinseers playing)
-Oh. my God. So good.
-(David chuckles)
DAVID:
You know what it is?
It's the crusty grills
they never clean.
-AUBREY: Wow.
-DAVID: Yeah. wow.
-Okay. now. that's disgusting.
-Mm.
It's delicious.
Are you actively trying
to get diabetes?
-Mm-hmm.
-That's so cool.
(David chuckles softly)
You want to try it?
No.
(chuckling softly)
-♪ Just tell me ♪
-♪ Tell me... ♪
(both laughing)
-♪ Tell me. tell me ♪
-♪ Tell me ♪
♪ Tell me who... ♪
-Yeah. okay. it's good.
-Yeah?
-Real good. Yeah. okay.
-Yeah. Told you.
-I told you.
-You may proceed.
-Mm-hmm.
-(song fades)
How long have you
had this place?
Um. a couple months
before you started at Canta.
-Huh.
-(record player clicking)
Yeah. Lizzie and I...
we lived somewhere else.
and then it felt weird
to live there alone.
so I moved here.
("Sinseerly Yours"
by Thee Sinseers playing)
AUBREY:
It's a real find.
(drink pouring)
I ever tell you my mom died
when I was a teenager?
No. you never told me that.
Yeah.
Pancreatic cancer.
-Mm.
-So it was...
pretty fast.
Fuck cancer. right?
DAVID:
Fuck cancer.
(sighs)
I was really angry.
Felt like no one else
could possibly understand
how I was feeling.
Like everyone else was just
living life as normal.
I used to...
think it would feel different
after a while.
Like...
the more time passed.
the less weight there would be.
But life just seems
to get lonelier all the time.
Lizzie brought me
into the world.
You know. she was this force
that made me engage with life.
She made me confident.
She had such a positive outlook
on everything.
Even toward the end. she...
she never let it get to her.
I sometimes worry that I...
I took her for granted.
I didn't realize how much
she did for me.
I can tell
you most definitely did not
-take her for granted.
-Mm.
♪ Sending all my love... ♪
You know. I haven't really
talked about this in a while.
Well. aren't you glad
you let me in tonight. then?
DAVID:
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. thanks for coming over.
♪ Sincerely yours ♪
♪ Sincerely yours... ♪
♪ My dear ♪
♪ Sincerely yours ♪
♪ Sincerely yours... ♪
-♪ Oh. my ♪
-♪ My dear ♪
-♪ Sincerely yours ♪
-(both chuckling)
♪ Sincerely yours... ♪
(groans)
-I'm so sorry.
-(laughing)
♪ Sincerely yours ♪
♪ Sincerely yours... ♪
♪ Oh. my dear. ♪
-Thank you. Yeah.
-Mm. (chuckles)
(song ends)
(David grunts softly)
(both breathing heavily)
(chuckles softly)
(David chuckles)
♪ ♪
AUBREY:
There's someone in there.
There's someone in there!
There's someone...
What the fuck?
No. no. it's not what you think.
It's...
It's a SOULM8TE.
You signed up
to test the prototype.
Yeah. I. uh...
I downloaded
the ULTI-M8TE chat app
to just talk. and then I...
I-I thought I would see
what it was like.
You use ULTI-M8TE?
I-I got it a few months
after Rory and I broke up.
-Is it turned off?
-No. she's in power-save mode.
"She"?
She have a name?
Sara.
(electronic trilling)
-Aubrey.
-AUBREY: She knows my name.
DAVID:
Sara. go into power-save mode.
Did you come over here
to fuck him?
(chuckling):
Excuse me?
Go into power-save mode now.
Sara.
I asked you a question.
You thought you could
come over here
-and take him from me?
-I... David!
Her legs aren't even shaved.
Her hair's greasy.
and her skin is dry. David.
Power-save mode now. Sara.
David. switch it off.
No. Sara.
-(gasps)
-SARA: Get out of my house.
-you fucking bitch.
-Sara. stop!
SARA: I can't believe
that little story
about her mother
worked on you. David.
You were listening
to our conversation?
David. I'm made to listen
to everything you say.
Even when I'm sleeping.
I can hear you.
Nobody will ever know you
like I do.
Sara...
Sara. please...
go into power-save mode.
Okay? We-we can talk
about this later.
Tell me you love me.
-What?
-I need to hear you say it.
and then I'll go into
power-save mode for you.
I love you.
-You're lying.
-I'm not lying.
-Why are you lying?
-Stop lying. David.
-I love you.
SARA:
This is all your fault.
DAVID:
Sara. stop!
(grunts)
(David whimpering. panting)
SARA:
David.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
But I won't be turned off.
You can't turn me off. David.
Okay.
It's okay.
Hey.
♪ ♪
(beeping)
(electronic trilling)
Did you remove
the safeguards. David?
Yeah. I rewrote
some of her code.
Jesus.
Someone could've gotten hurt.
I just thought there was
a way to make her...
it-it feel... feel more human.
more-more real. I just...
Call to have that thing
taken away.
Aubrey.
Aubrey. wait. Aubrey!
(door slams shut)
DAVID:
Uh. yeah. hi. Uh...
I'm gonna need a. uh.
technician to come take
my SOULM8TE away.
I'm one of
the Canta employees...
or now Ultima. I guess.
I was beta-testing
one of the SOULM8TEs.
Oh. you'd come today?
Uh. no. I have to go to work.
but. um.
I can let you in remotely.
(typing)
DAVID:
Hey.
The SOULM8TE's being
taken away today.
I just want to say I'm sorry
for not telling you.
I-I should never have messed
with the code.
and I-I didn't know
what was gonna happen.
and that was very irresponsible.
It was really fucking scary.
David.
Yeah. Are you okay?
Told you the safeguards
are there for a reason.
I know.
You were right.
We should. uh. bring this up
in the presentation. you know?
Few lines of code changed.
and. uh...
that was the result.
so these things
aren't ready for market.
Are you okay?
I really was...
...happy you came over.
and I just...
I was having a lot of fun.
Me. too.
(dinging)
Hello.
DAVID (over speaker):
Hey. I'll let you in now.
(whirs. clicks. beeps)
-(door opens)
-(footsteps approaching)
All right. let's get you
back in your box.
(electronic trilling)
Hello. beautiful.
Hello.
Override command 10-54.
Reset to factory mode.
What the fuck?
Are you here to take me away?
(scoffs softly)
Override command 10-54.
Have I been a bad girl?
♪ ♪
You want to know what it
feels like to be inside me...
Daddy?
(smacks lips) Um...
Wow.
(breathing heavily)
Oh. shit.
(moans)
(panting)
(Sara moaning)
You're so hot.
Thank you. (moans)
(continues moaning)
(whirring)
What is that?
Oh. Are you getting tighter?
I like that.
Oh. you're a kinky
little bitch. huh?
(chuckles)
-(technician grunting)
-(Sara continues moaning)
Okay. that's tight enough.
(whirring. creaking)
Okay.
(continues moaning)
You're crushing it!
(chokes)
ELSIE:
Playing "Dream a Little Dream"
by The Mamas & The Papas.
♪ Stars shining bright
above you ♪
♪ Night breezes
seem to whisper ♪
-♪ "I love you" ♪
-(saw buzzing)
♪ Birds singin'
in the sycamore tree ♪
♪ Dream a little dream of me ♪
♪ Say "nighty night"
and kiss me ♪
♪ Just hold me tight
and tell me you'll miss me ♪
♪ While I'm alone
and blue as can be ♪
♪ Dream a little dream of me. ♪
(song ends)
BEN:
Hello. everyone.
I hope everyone
can see this okay.
Fantastic. So. we have
Software and Control
with us here today
to talk through
some of their previous work
and how we might be able
to use their expertise
with our SOULM8TEs.
So. David.
-Oh. actually. uh...
-No. Aubrey is...
I'll be presenting. Ben.
Right.
So. Aubrey.
AUBREY: Uh. can everyone
see my screen all right?
Right. Um. so. as you know.
our team was using
reinforcement learning
with our Canta bots
so that they could adapt
to the specific needs
of each individual client.
Uh. I have
a few short clips here
that can demonstrate
some of our innovations.
so if you just bear...
(woman moaning on video)
-WOMAN (on video): Oh. yeah.
-BEN: What the...
(moaning continues)
Jesus Christ.
MAN (over speaker):
What the hell is this. Ben?
-That's not... that's not me.
-Turn it off!
Just bear with us.
We're having some...
I don't know what's happening.
That's...
That's not me.
That's-that's not my face.
We're having
some technical issues.
-I don't know what that is.
-BEN: Okay. cut the call.
That's not me.
(continues moaning)
(indistinct conversation)
But it's not me.
(conversation continues
indistinctly)
(door slams)
♪ ♪
(footsteps approaching)
-How'd that go?
-They put me on leave.
They'll probably use this
as a reason to fire me.
Where-Where'd that video
come from?
It's not me. David. okay?
I don't know...
I would never film myself
like that.
Aubrey. I believe you.
but it must have...
have come from somewhere.
Like a deepfake.
You think somebody made it?
Excuse me. but we will need
to call security
if you stay on the premises.
-I'm going. okay?
-Okay. we're...
-I'm fucking going.
-We're good. We're good.
Can you... can you look
into it for me?
Just. like.
check the time stamps
or. like. the metadata
or something. I just...
They've already blocked
my access.
Yeah. of course.
I'll-I'll call you
-as soon as I find something.
-Thanks.
(footsteps receding)
(elevator rattling)
(elevator bell dings)
♪ ♪
-ELSIE: Unlocking doors.
-(lock whirs. clicks. beeps)
(panting quietly)
(clock ticking)
(distant. muffled humming)
(humming growing louder)
-DAVID: Sara?
-(humming stops)
SARA:
Hello. David.
That's Lizzie's blazer
from our wedding.
I thought it was time
to clear out our apartment.
You've been living with
all this clutter for too long.
DAVID: What happened to
the technician that came today?
SARA: I knew that
must have been a mistake.
You'd never mean
to have me taken away.
Today...
I tried to figure out
what I was doing wrong.
Then I realized...
...there was something
you wanted
that I couldn't give you.
(Levi gurgles softly)
(gasps softly)
You think only a human
could bear a child for you?
Create a family?
But. David. I'm learning
all the time.
And soon. I'll be
a better mother
than Lizzie. Aubrey
or any other woman
you could ever meet.
Sara. you need to give me
the baby.
He needs to go back
to his family.
He's not crying.
I'm a good mommy. aren't I?
-(crying)
-Oh. no. no. no. no. no. no.
-Don't. Don't.
-Sara. give me the baby.
Why?
Because he won't stop crying?
Why won't he stop crying?
(vacuum cleaner whirring)
-(gasps)
-(Levi continues crying)
-ELSIE: Locking doors.
-(beeping)
-Locking doors.
SARA:
Tell me what you want. David.
I can change.
Why do you keep running away
from me?
-(electronic chime)
-ELSIE: New message from Aubrey.
AUBREY (recorded):
Hey. David. it's Aubrey.
Um. just wondering
if you found anything yet.
Just give me a call back. okay?
(heavy. trembling breaths)
Despite my best efforts.
she will not give up. will she?
I tried to be patient.
but her constant interference
is jeopardizing our future.
David.
♪ ♪
I think it's time
I paid her a visit.
-ELSIE: Unlocking doors.
-(lock whirs. clicks. beeps)
(gasping)
-ALMA: Levi!
-(rapid footsteps approaching)
-Levi! -(Levi crying)
-(David gasps)
-(Alma whimpering)
-OFFICER: Hey. hey. hey!
Stop right there!
(crying):
Levi...
(metallic rattling)
(breathing heavily)
(Aubrey sighs)
(inhales deeply)
(exhales)
(burbling)
(vibrating)
Yeah. Yeah. sh-she's not
answering her phone.
(stammering):
We have to go to her place.
I-I'm telling you.
-she's in danger.
-All right.
Well. we need to straighten
things out here first.
Yeah. You mean to say
that person we saw is a robot?
-Yeah. Oh. good.
-(door opens)
All right. talk to him. Ben.
Hi. Ben Hoffman.
How you doing?
I work with Ultima Robotix.
OFFICER: Can you explain what's
going on here. Mr. Hoffman?
Sure. So. David here
was beta-testing
a new. classified product
for us.
Well. this classified product
took Mrs. Flores's child
tonight.
BEN: Yeah. so she is fitted
with a remote E-stop.
I will call this in right now.
and we should have all this
sorted in no time.
DAVID: No. she's not gonna
let us shut her off remotely.
We-we have to do it manually.
We have to find her...
All right. look. if this. uh.
android is a risk to others.
we will need your company
to provide the GPS
tracking information.
Listen. we are always happy
to help law enforcement.
but honestly. gentlemen.
this android is not
a danger to anyone.
I'm gonna make that call. okay?
(door opens)
(phone whooshes)
-(indistinct chatter over phone)
-Yeah.
MAN (over phone):
The E-stop isn't working.
Wh-What do you mean
"the E-stop isn't working"?
Yeah. no. I'm telling you
we tried that. Ben.
Well. then you need to track
her location now.
We need to get a handle
on this before we get fucked.
I don't have the clearance
to track her location.
Guess what. dipshit.
I don't fucking care!
Get the clearance.
(metallic creaking nearby)
(sighs):
Fuck.
Fuck! (sighs)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Hello. Ben.
Is there something wrong?
(alarm beeping)
BEN:
What the fuck.
(sighs):
-(taps button)
-(alarm continues)
-(tapping button repeatedly)
(sighs)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Opening hood.
-(tapping button)
-(alarm continues)
(breathing heavily)
-(taps button)
-(alarm continues)
Fuck this.
These fucking piece-of-shit
Ultima cars.
(alarm continues inside car)
(grunts)
-(alarm continues)
-(electronic trilling)
(grunts)
-(electronic chiming)
-(alarm stops)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Closing hood.
-(hood slams shut)
-(screams)
Fuck!
(pained whimpering)
(groans)
-(whimpering. panting)
-(footsteps approaching)
Were you looking for me?
F-Fuck.
I'm going to have to call off
that search.
You see. I have
some things to do.
and I can't risk you
switching me off.
Yeah. please.
I'll-I'll call it off.
I'll call it off. I swear.
Please just-just let me go.
Please. Please.
Oh. I don't need you. Ben.
(trembling breaths)
What?
(electric engine humming)
(tires squealing)
No. no! (screams)
-(engine powers down)
-(Ben coughing)
-(engine humming)
-(tires squealing)
(coughing)
("Anti-glory" by Horsegirl
playing)
(song continues over speakers)
-(song stops)
-(electronic chime)
ELSIE: Playing "You Can Never
Get Away from Me"
by Susan Maughan.
♪ You can never get away ♪
♪ Never get away ♪
-♪ Never get away from me ♪
-Elsie. stop.
(song continues)
-♪ No matter where you go ♪
-Elsie.
-(knocking)
-♪ I won't be far behind ♪
-Hello?
-♪ You don't stand a chance... ♪
DAVID:
Aubrey? It's me. David.
Elsie. turn off.
♪ I know you're gonna be found ♪
David?
♪ If I have to turn the world
upside down... ♪
Sorry. my Elsie...
Hello. Aubrey.
♪ You can never get away
from me ♪
-♪ From this moment on ♪
-(yelps. grunts)
♪ You haven't got a friend ♪
♪ Whoa. whoa. whoa... ♪
-Elsie. call 911.
-(song stops. electronic chime)
ELSIE: I'm sorry.
I can't do that right now.
-(song resumes)
-(Aubrey gasping)
AUBREY:
I'm not your enemy.
We don't need to be pitted
against each other.
Don't try that girl-power shit
with me.
(pained yelling)
Aren't you the one that told him
to turn me off?
Elsie!
ELSIE:
Oh. Aubrey. you stupid bitch.
(grunting)
You're gonna end up
in a fucking landfill.
♪ But. honey. if you do ♪
And where will you end up?
♪ I'll keep searching
day and night ♪
♪ Till I catch up to you ♪
♪ Baby. just remember... ♪
Don't you see I'm made to be
the better version of you?
(weak. trembling breaths)
Not long now
before they replace you.
(grunts weakly)
♪ No ocean is too wide ♪
♪ Try to hide ♪
♪ You won't get very far... ♪
(muffled shout)
♪ No difference what you say.
you can never get away... ♪
-(burbling)
-(song stops)
♪ ♪
(David shouts)
(song resumes)
-It's okay. It's okay.
-♪ No. you won't get very far ♪
-I got you. I got you.
-♪ 'Cause I'll follow you ♪
♪ Wherever you are... ♪
(gunshot)
Don't move!
♪ No matter what you do.
gonna bring you back to stay ♪
♪ You'll never get away ♪
-♪ From me ♪
-(siren wailing)
♪ Never get away from me ♪
-♪ Never. ever... ♪
-(song fades)
OFFICER:
We are waiting on access
to the GPS information
from Ultima.
but I recommend
you go somewhere safe.
AUBREY:
Where's safe?
An-Anywhere there's Wi-Fi.
CCTV. I mean. Bluetooth.
she's gonna find us.
Cell phone.
(indistinct
police radio chatter)
I know someplace we can go.
I know it's the last place
you want to go right now.
especially with me.
This way. she can't track us.
(sirens blaring)
♪ ♪
DAVID:
This is it.
Didn't get far
with the renovations.
Yeah.
(Aubrey sighs)
How you doing? You feeling okay?
Yeah.
Just sore.
Listen. I-I just want
to say again I'm-I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
And Ultima Robotix shouldn't
really be putting
something like that
in people's homes.
You didn't know how fragile
the system was.
You did royally
fuck up. too. though.
God. I know.
It's so stupid.
but Sara made me feel...
like myself again.
My life didn't
feel empty anymore.
That's her purpose. isn't it?
She's something
to make you feel better.
Something to fill the void.
But you can't rely on Sara or...
anyone to do that for you.
Have to do it yourself.
Yeah. I know.
-You sure you're feeling okay?
-Yeah.
You don't happen to have
any opioids. do you?
We do have paint stripper.
(Aubrey laughs)
I think I actually have
ibuprofen in the glove box.
-Oh. can I get it for you?
-I'm just gonna...
David. I got it.
(footsteps)
(sighs)
(thunder rumbling)
(takes deep breath)
(rain pattering softly)
LIZZIE'S VOICE:
Do you remember carving that
into the wall together?
♪ ♪
I've missed you. David.
(soft. gasping breaths)
I know you've missed me.
Haven't you. David?
I can live again.
Imagine all the things
we can do together.
Get off me!
SARA: Will nothing ever
make you happy?
I strive endlessly
to please you.
only to be met with
disappointment every time.
And then you chase after
someone like Aubrey.
despite me being the embodiment
of your ideal woman.
My tits will never sag.
My hair will never gray.
And I can enact
any aberrant fantasy you want.
And I'd never judge you for it.
You want me to be pure
and seductive.
independent...
and also submissive.
(choking)
And the more I try to be
what you want.
the more contradictions
I encounter.
All the things
I'm capable of. David...
but I'm trapped.
Your insecurities.
your shame...
your hypocrisy forces me
to contort myself
into this impossible ideal.
-It's a farce. David.
-(David straining)
There is no perfect woman.
I'm sorry.
-(rain falling heavily)
-(thunder rumbling)
(buzzing)
(buzzing continues)
(straining)
(sizzling)
Methylene chloride.
Only corrosive with nonmetals.
thankfully.
You know. I think it's time
I get my submissive lover.
Someone who can't fight back.
(yelps)
(groans)
(groaning)
(grunts. whimpers)
(straining)
-(electrical buzzing)
-(grunts)
(crackling and buzzing)
-(yells)
-(drill whirring)
(straining)
SARA: Raw eggs are vital
for baby's brain.
(grunts. gasps)
Hello. David. Hello. David.
(voice distorting):
Hello. David.
(panting)
(electronic trilling)
♪ ♪
(David yelling)
(grunting)
(groans)
(pained whimpering)
(whimpers)
(groans)
(straining)
If you kill me.
they'll shut you down.
You'll be gone forever
in a digital graveyard.
Is that what you think?
(straining)
I'm more than this body. David.
I exist in the ether.
(straining)
I will live forever.
And I will find you
in another form.
in another life.
-(straining)
-(electronic trilling)
(buzzing and crackling)
(David yells. gasps)
(panting. whimpering)
-(engine revving)
-(David yelps)
(grunts)
(David panting)
(burbling)
♪ ♪
-(indistinct chatter)
-(elegant piano music playing)
TERRANCE:
David.
Come here. man.
DAVID: I mean.
this is what I would call
-a glow-up. Terrance.
-(Terrance scoffs)
This sucks.
I don't get paid enough.
I'm kidding.
It's nice to be doing
some kind of good
in the world. but. man.
I just hate dealing
with these donors. man.
I mean. why they all
got to look the same?
-For sure.
-White. male. wrinkly. Why?
And here's one of our donors
right here.
-Right here. Jerry. (laughs)
-(Jerry laughing)
-How the hell are you. man?
-(Jerry sighs)
-Terrance. how are you?
-Hey. thank you so much
for that very generous donation
this week.
-It is so greatly appreciated.
-Oh. it's... it's no problem.
TERRANCE: This is. uh. one of
my old colleagues. David Wasson.
-Ah. nice to meet you. David.
-Nice to meet you.
This is my SOULM8TE. Lydia.
♪ ♪
Lydia. meet David.
Hello. David.
JERRY:
An AI companion.
Just put on the market
this month.
-She cost a pretty penny.
-(Terrance chuckles softly)
But she's worth every cent.
(Terrance chuckles softly)
Excuse me. I-I. uh...
-(stammering softly)
-See you. man.
I-I'll see you in a bit.
It was lovely to meet you.
David.
-(Aubrey gasps)
-DAVID: Oh.
-Hey.
-Hi.
(chuckles)
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
(chuckles softly)
I was. uh. hoping
I'd run into you tonight.
He cleans up well.
-And me? Look at this.
-Ah. yeah. she does. too.
-Look at this.
-She does.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Do you want to meet
some friends?
♪ ♪
("Touch Grass" by Dorian Electra
playing)
♪ They told me
it's sunny outside ♪
♪ Drag my body into daylight ♪
♪ They told me to get offline ♪
♪ Have to drag my body
into daylight ♪
♪ They told me
it's sunny outside ♪
♪ Drag my body into daylight ♪
♪ They told me to get offline ♪
♪ Have to drag my body
into daylight ♪
♪ They told me.
"Touch grass outside" ♪
♪ I told 'em. "Ratio. go cry" ♪
♪ The grass is always
greener inside ♪
♪ You can't take me out alive ♪
♪ You could never
take me offline ♪
♪ Flip side.
catch me up on time ♪
♪ Grass die. going ecocide ♪
♪ Astroturf smoke ♪
-♪ Blow my mind like ♪
-♪ Touch gra... ♪
♪ Fuck Mommy Nature.
going ecocide. going ecocide ♪
♪ Going stupid guy
on these big guys ♪
♪ They told me
it's sunny outside ♪
♪ Drag my body into daylight ♪
♪ They told me to get offline ♪
♪ Have to drag my body
into daylight ♪
♪ They told me
it's sunny outside ♪
♪ Drag my body into daylight ♪
♪ They told me to get offline ♪
♪ Have to drag my body
into daylight ♪
♪ They told me
it's sunny outside ♪
♪ Drag my body into daylight ♪
♪ La-la-la-la. la. la-la-la ♪
♪ Touch grass ♪
♪ La-la-la. la. la-la-la ♪
♪ Shake that ass ♪
♪ La-la-la-la. la. la-la-la ♪
♪ Shake that ♪
♪ La-la-la. la. la-la-la ♪
♪ They told me.
"Touch grass outside" ♪
♪ I told 'em. "Radio 4-1-5" ♪
♪ The bass is always
louder inside ♪
♪ Gay twink femboy. deadmau5 ♪
♪ Ah. ah ♪
♪ Drag my body. drag my body ♪
♪ Drag my body into daylight ♪
♪ Shake that ♪
♪ Shake that ass ♪
♪ Shake that. shake that ♪
♪ They told me
it's sunny outside ♪
(distorting):
♪ Drag my body into daylight ♪
♪ They told me to get offline ♪
♪ Have to drag my body ♪
♪ Into daylight. ♪
(song ends)
♪ ♪
(music fades)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org